翻譯: melody
我剛剛搞到兩張
Hey, I just got us 2 tickets
布拉德皮特新電影首映式的票
to the premiere of the new Brad pitt movie.
校對: 怪查理
Nikki
Nikki...
到時候會有記者 會有攝影師
There'll be reporters there. There'll be photographers.
后期: 東仔
人們會看到咱倆在一起
People will see us together.
所以呢
So?
所以
So...
壓制: 猴給力
我們是地下情
We're having a secret relationship.
天吶 你太不擅長這個了
God, you suck at this.
以前我們老是一起出去
We used to hang out all the time before.
那是在我們上床以前
Yeah, well, that was before we were sleeping together.
我們那時候 是朋友
We were... Friends then.
所以現在我們上床了 就不是朋友了
Oh, so now that we're sleeping together, we can't be friends.
我可不和朋友上床 Nikki
I don't have sex with my friends, Nikki.
我不是禽獸
I'm not an animal.
我只是受夠一直偷偷摸摸的了
I'm just tired of sneaking around all the time.
甜心 我們這是謹慎
Sweetie, we're being cautious.
這叫慎重 好嗎
We're being prudent, ok?
這不一樣
There's a difference.
偷偷摸摸
Sneaking around.
拜托 Nikki
Come on, Nikki.
我現在要走了
All right, I'm gonna leave now,
你
so you, uh...
五分鐘之后在市場的拐角處和我匯合
Wait 5 minutes meet me at the market around the corner.
還有 Nikki 跟以前一樣 如果我拿著一個菠蘿
And, Nikki, as always, if I'm holding a pineapple,
約會取消
abort.
政界小人物
第三季 第十九集
電波誠譯
Paul 你為什么遲到
Hey, Paul. Why are you late?
這 這顯得一天不那么漫長
I... It makes the day seem shorter.
早 上 好
Go-o-o-ood morning.
Mike Nikki每天都遲到
Mike, Nikki's late every day.
你從來不為難她
You never get on her.
不用你操心 Paul
Oh, don't you worry, Paul.
他今天一早就"調教"過我了
He got on me earlier this morning.
下次 我很樂意見識一下
Well, next time, Mike, I'd like to see that.
不知怎么的 我覺得再也沒心情了
Somehow, I think that might ruin it for me.
你從體育商店買了什么
Hey, what did you get at the sports depot?
給我男朋友買了一根跳繩
Just a jump rope for this guy I'm seeing.
他是個正在訓練的運動員
He's an athlete, and he's in training.
厄
Hmm...
備戰超級花式跳繩錦標賽嗎
Big double Dutch tournament?
Nikki 你桌上是我的鋼筆嗎
Nikki, is that my... my pen on your desk?
你竟然穿了我的襯衫
You're wearing my shirt!
那又怎樣 沒人會注意的
So what? No one's gonna notice.
上面繡著我的名字
It's monogrammed!
Nikki 我找到你想要的文件了
Nikki, I found that file you wanted.
你捂住你的胸干嘛
Why are you holding your breast?
早些 它們中有一個想逃跑
Earlier, one of them tried to get away.
你有才
Cool.
Mike 市長上<新聞熱議間>的提要
Ok, Mike, I'm done with the mayor's notes
一檔真實存在的談話節目 本集中由主持人Bill Maher真人客串
我已經寫好了
for his appearance on politically incorrect.
干得好 James
Great, James.
政治要求知己知彼
You see, politics is all about preparation.
出其不意是你最大的敵人
Surprise is your worst enemy.
沒有任何人 任何人 能讓Mike Flaherty吃驚
And nobody, I mean nobody, surprises Mike Flaherty.
啊
Ahhh!
怎么了
What?
沒事 就是清清喉嚨
Nothing. Just clearing my throat.
啊
Ahhh!
有了陳年的面包
So, with day-old rolls,
一些變硬的花生醬
some dehydrated peanut paste
再加上從餐館偷來的果凍
and some stolen jelly packets from the diner,
我覺得我能給自己來一頓
I figure I can give myself a nourishing lunch
一天8分錢的營養午餐
for about 8 cents a day.
比Sally Struthers提供的伙食好多了
That's better than Sally Struthers.
激進分子 臭名昭著的兒童組織ChildFund的代言人
Paul 我打賭你想嘗嘗這些
Paul, I bet you wish you had one of these babies.
意大利肉丸三明治
An Italian meatball sub.
那樣的三明治 得多少錢 5或6美元
A sandwich like that, that's what? 5, 6 dollars?
我才不會浪費那么多錢在午餐上
I don't pay that kind of money for lunch.
你買西裝都沒花過這么多錢
You don't pay that kind of money for suits.
我祖母給我做的
My grandmother makes these for me.
讓人上癮
They are so addictive.
你才會上癮 你知道為什么嗎
Addictive for you. You know why?
因為你是個女人
'Cause you're a woman,
而且你沒有定力
and you're weak.
嘗嘗
Here.
沒感覺
Nothing.
再咬一大口
Another massive bite.
還是沒感覺
Nothing.
我們什么時候和市長談談
So, Mike, when are we gonna talk to the mayor?
等會 我現在有點不舒服
Uh, later. I don't feel so good right now.
啊
Ahhh!
哥們 你真的應該去檢查下你的喉嚨
Boy, you really oughta have someone take a look at that throat.
你搞什么
What are you doing?
你不想讓別人看見我穿你的襯衫 那我就脫咯
You didn't want people to see me in your shirt, so I took it off.
Nikki
Nikki...
我在抗議 Mike
I'm protesting, Mike.
我想告訴大家咱倆的事
I wanna tell people about us.
我知道會有點棘手
I know it's gonna be awkward,
但你知道嗎 我不在乎
but you know what? I don't care.
我才不怕呢 我希望每個人都知道
I'm not scared. I want everyone to know.
嘿 Mike
Hey, Mike.
哼 你就是嘴上說說
Oh, you're all talk.
讓我跟你們解釋一下
Let me explain something to ya.
那家伙失去意識九個小時了
The dude was out cold for 9 hours.
所以 技術上來說 那不叫倒地
Now, technically, that ain't no knockout.
那叫昏迷
That's a coma.
看看這是誰啊 哪位猛男
Hey, what are you, some kind of tough guy?
要是崇拜者們想要看好戲 我必須效勞
Oh, please. When the minions demand a show, I must oblige.
我給你帶了點東西
Yeah, I brought you something.
你不喜歡嗎
You don't like it?
Carter 你不能在體育館里給我送禮物
Carter, you can't bring me gifts at the gym.
Bennet 現在是1999年
Bennet, it's 1999.
人們對同性戀運動員很寬容的
People are very open-minded about gay athletes.
你看我像一個花樣滑冰運動員嗎
Do I look like a figure skater to you?
拳擊也是與時俱進的
Oh, boxing is totally geared toward our community.
兩個帥哥穿著綢緞長袍出場(出柜)
Two attractive men come out in satin robes.
他們貼身肉搏
They dance around for awhile,
贏家可以提著裝滿錢的小手袋扭回家
the winner gets to take home a purse.
你說的可是我的夢想
This is my dream you're talking about here.
但你不需要否認你是怎樣的人
Yeah, but you don't have to deny who you are.
你還可以像Mike一樣
You can still be like Mike...
即使你像Mike一樣
Even if you like Mike.
我要賺錢 我要贏得冠軍
I'm gonna make some money, get ranked,
等他們誰都不能瞧不起我的時候
and then, when they can't get rid of me,
相信我 我站上巔峰的時候 我會出柜
believe me, I'm gonna come out... big time.
這樣你能接受嗎
Can you accept that?
我想可以
Yeah, I guess so.
Bennet 怎么樣 今晚打算干什么
Yo, Bennet. What's up? Whatcha doin' tonight, man?
你是說我今晚要干誰嗎 哈哈
You mean who am I gonna do tonight? Ha ha.
哪個幸運的女人
What lucky lady's gonna get
能得到Bennet男神的全方位寵幸呢
the all night, airtight, Bennet boom boom express?
保重 Bennet
Take care, Bennet.
哈哈哈哈哈哈
Ha ha ha. Ha ha ha.
都是逢場作戲而已 寶貝
It's all part of the show, sweetie.
Mike 我知道你看見我和Janelle親嘴了
Look, Mike, I know that you saw janelle and I kissing...
不可能
no way.
可能 Mike
Yes way, Mike.
我希望得到你的祝福
I hope you'll give us your blessing.
先生 你不能和Janelle約會 你是她的老板
Sir, you can't date janelle. You're her boss.
那太齷齪了
It's... it's sleazy.
嗷
Ow!
我得站起來走走才能消化這事 先生
I gotta get up and walk this off, sir.
你不覺得你現在有點虛偽嗎
Don't you think you're being a little hypocritical here?
你 你知道什么了
No... why, what do you know?
三個月前 你看上了那個
Well, I know that 3 months ago, you were fantasizing about
年輕金發碧眼的臨時工 Molly
that young, blonde temp, Molly,
而且你還想約她出去
and you tried asking her out.
幸虧我現在是站著的
I... I'm glad I'm standing up.
快看 我最愛的杯子從我桌子上摔下來了
Oh, look at that. My favorite mug just fell off my desk.
幸好沒摔碎
I'm glad it didn't break.
又反彈了
Second bounce.
你終于來了
Oh, there you are.
你必須得再給我一個肉丸三明治
You gotta hook me up with another meatball sandwich, ok?
我像染了毒癮一樣
I'm jonesin' bad.
沒問題 給你
Ok, ok. Here you go.
多謝
Thanks.
20美元
That'll be $20.
昨天你怎么不收錢
What about yesterday?
第一個總是免費的
First one's always free.
來吧
And here...
嘗嘗這醬汁
Take a hit off the sauce.
噢
Oh, yeah...
Oh, yeah. Oh...
純正的醬汁
Oh, that's pure.
- 大家好啊  - 嗨
- Hey, everybody.  - Hey.
你在干嘛 你不是在準備笑話吧
What are you doing? You're not working on jokes, are ya?
Bill 紐約市長不需要準備笑話
Bill, the mayor of New York does not need to prepare jokes.
他就是政壇上最搞笑的人之一
He's one of the funniest men in politics.
真的 我猜你從沒看過
Really? I guess you never saw
美國供職時間最長的參議員
Strom Thurmond穿著運動褲的樣子
strom thurmond in his gym shorts.
有意思
That's funny.
記下來
Jot that down.
無意冒犯 你不應該費心彩排
Hey, if I may, you shouldn't try to over-rehearse this.
這節目宗旨就是即興發揮
The show's all about the spontaneity.
用不著擔心我
Well, don't worry about me.
我通常都不知道自己想說什么
I usually don't know what I'm going to say until...
說完好久我才能反應過來
Long after I've actually said it.
不錯
Good.
聽著 我要加個話題
Ok, listen, I'm gonna add a topic.
我聽說警察昨晚闖進了哈萊姆區(黑人聚居區)
I read about the police sweep in Harlem last night,
隨機逮捕了67個人
the 67 random arrests.
等等 等等 你不
No, wait, wait. You can't...
你不能想加話題就隨便加話題
you can't just add topics whenever you feel like it.
我當然能 Mike 這就是我的工作
Of course I can, Mike. That's what I do here.
那么 我說
Well, then, I think the
市長突然身體不適
mayor is suddenly coming down with something.
不 我沒病 Mike
No, I'm ok, Mike.
伙計 放松 在<政治熱議間>
Fellas, relax. On politically incorrect,
你不需要做一個專家
you don't have to be an expert.
你只需要有自己的看法就行了
You just have to have an opinion.
現在 市長先生 你是想坐我左邊還是坐我右邊呢
Now, Mr. Mayor, would you like to sit to my left or to my right?
我決定坐你右邊
I'm gonna go with the right.
這就對了 Bennet 打倒他
Hey, that's right, Bennet. Mess him up.
上帝
Oh, my God!
你的臉蛋啊 你漂亮的臉蛋
Your face! Your beautiful face!
我是說
Uh... I mean, uh...
你以后可怎么泡妞啊 兄弟
How you gonna nail all them chicks now, dude?
等一下
Hold on a second.
昨晚 你的警察局長逮捕了超過六十名非裔美國人
Last night, your police chief arrested over 60 African-Americans
拘留了他們2個小時查他們的案底
and detained them for 2 hours while their records were checked.
你不覺得這個行為讓人不恥嗎
You don't consider that revolting?
你見過Strom Thurmond穿運動短褲的樣子嗎
Have you ever seen strom thurmond in his gym shorts?
先生 想想你的三大絕招
All right, sir. Remember your 3 ds...
回避 閃躲 不承認
deflect, dodge, and deny.
哇哇哇 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
你說什么
You were saying?
警察局長為你工作 市長先生
The police chief works for you, Mr. Mayor.
你知道那些政策說明了什么嗎
And you know what that kind of policy says to me?
那表明你是個種族主義者
It says that you're a racist.
別胡扯了 我才不是種族主義者
Oh, don't be ridiculous. I'm not a racist.
我1963年來到華盛頓
I marched on Washington in '63.
我畢生都致力于支持平權法案
I have supported affirmative action my entire career.
對 先生 你快說服他們了 趕緊扯開話題
There you go, sir. You got 'em on the run. Now lower the boom.
事實上
In fact...
我在和一個黑人女性約會
I'm dating a black woman.
完蛋了
Boom.
那 那是誰
And... and, who would that be?
別說 先生 別別別 別說
Don't say it, sir. Don't... don't... don't say it, don't say it.
我的秘書
My secretary.
好 短暫休息一下
Ok, well... We will take a break,
我們馬上回來
and we will be right back.
成功躲過一劫 是吧 Mike
Dodged that bullet, huh, Mike?
Janelle 抱歉 我應該提前和你打好招呼的
Janelle, I'm so sorry. I should have talked to you first.
你當時很緊張 我理解
Oh, you were nervous. I understand.
我要好好補償你
Well, let me make it up to you.
我們去之前看到的那家意大利餐廳吧
We'll go to that Italian restaurant we saw.
Umberto那家
Umberto's?
我會訂一個靠著壁爐的好桌位
I'll get you a nice-a table by the fireplace-a.
你們好啊 Ross和Rachel
Hey Ross, Rachel.
經典美劇<老友記>中的情侶
我來只是想說
Hi, um, I just wanted to come in and say
我覺得兩個工作在一起的人
that I think it's great two people who work together
有一段公開坦誠的感情真是太好了
are having an open and honest relationship.
但我覺得那種
Well, I think that relationships
有可能毀了他們自己的事業的感情
that could potentially ruin people's professional careers
應該要保密
should be left confidential.
保密多久
For how long?
五個月
5 months.
那么 我們現在怎么辦
So, what do we do now?
先生 這事不是我們想糊弄就能糊弄過去的
Well, sir, it's not like we can just make it go away.
面對現實吧
I mean, let's face it.
一切都覆水難收了
You let the genie out of the bottle.
不不不 我們只親過嘴
Oh, no, no. We only kissed.
你好嗎 Carter
Hey, what's up, Carter?
James
Oh, James...
感情可真復雜
Romantic complications.
我正交往的人是個拳擊手
The guy I'm seeing is a boxer, and, uh...
昨天我一沖動
Yesterday I was overcome with emotion
不小心讓他出柜了
and I accidentally outed him.
我覺得 Bennet應該為他是誰而感到驕傲
Personally, I think Bennet should be proud of who he is,
不過 我可能永遠毀了他的事業
but, uh, I may have irreparably damaged his career.
結果是 我在乎這個男人
The bottom line is, I care about the guy,
但他沒有回我電話
and he's not returning my calls.
我永遠支持你 伙計
I'm here for ya, buddy.
那是個尷尬的時刻 卻讓我們沒把持住 吻了對方
It was an awkward moment, and somehow it led to a kiss.
但我們都是單身 有權交往的成年人
But we are both single, consenting adults,
如果我們選擇結為夫婦
and if we choose to move forward as a couple,
毫無疑問Cooper小姐
Ms. Cooper would undoubtedly
會在市政大廳換一份工作
take a different job here in city hall.
不過 我仍然會是市長
I, however, would still be the mayor.
- 市長先生  - 請講
- Mr. Mayor?  - Yes.
你為什么要跟我們坦白這些
Why are you being so up front with us?
我是政府官員
Well, I'm a public official.
盡可能的坦誠是我的職責
I feel it's my responsibility to be as Frank as possible.
Bob 我討厭你的發型
Bob... I hate your haircut.
要是真相流傳出來
You know, if this truth thing catches on,
我就要失業了
I'm gonna be out of a job.
- 請講  - 市長先生
- Yes?  - Mr. Mayor, are you going to continue
即使Cooper小姐仍然為你工作
having sexual relations with Ms. Cooper,
你也會和她發生性關系嗎
even while she's still working for you?
我們從沒發生過關系
Oh, we've never had sex.
誰信啊
Yeah, right.
不 我說真的
No, really. It's true.
我要你們聽我說 我再說一遍
I want you to listen to me. I'm gonna say this again.
模仿比爾克林頓對性丑聞的回應
我和那個女人沒有發生性關系
I did not have sexual relations with that woman...
也就是Cooper小姐
Ms. Cooper.
該吃午餐了 Paul
It's almost lunchtime, Paul.
感覺如何
How ya feeling?
走開
Get out.
我已經不在乎了
I'm over you.
你心里清楚你想吃這個
You know you want it.
我已經有完美的雞蛋沙拉三明治了 懂嗎
I've got a perfectly good egg salad sandwich, all right?
想要的都有
It's got everything you want...
除了 肉
Except meat...
丸
Balls.
天 天 你能行 你能行
Ok, ok, you're fine, you're fine, ok?
想也別想 放棄這個念頭
Don't even think about it. Put it out of your head.
肉
Meat...
丸
Ball.
肉
Meat...
丸
Ball.
肉
Meat...
丸
Ball...
三明治
Sandwich.
閉嘴 閉嘴
Ah! Shut up! Shut up!
你們都給我閉嘴
All of you, shut up!
先生 這是一個很簡單的補救措施
Look, sir, this is an easy fix.
你所需要做的就是回去告訴他們實話
All you gotta do is go back out there and tell them the truth.
我說的就是實話
I told them the truth. Yeah,
但不是他們想聽的實話
but it wasn't the truth they wanted to hear,
- 所以對他們來說那是謊言  - 我撒謊了嗎
- so to them it's a lie.  - I lied?
還沒 你要是不說那就只是一個謊言
Not yet. It's only a lie if you don't say it.
- 說什么  - 實話
- Say what?  - The truth.
- 誰的實話  - 他們的
- Whose truth?  - Theirs.
- 但那是謊言  - 對他們來說不是
- But it's a lie. - Not to them.
- 所以告訴他們實話  - 如果有助于你撒謊的話
- So tell them the truth?  - If it helps you lie.
Janelle 你聽明白了嗎
Janelle, are you getting any of this?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
我也是 我只是考考你
Me, too. I was just testing you.
先生 你只需要走回去
Look, sir, all you gotta do is go back out there
告訴他們你實際上和Janelle睡了
and tell them that you actually slept with janelle,
讓他們滿意 搞定
and it pops their whole balloon. It's over.
我不行 Mike 我沒Janelle上床
I can't do that, Mike. I didn't sleep with janelle,
我絕不會為了保住自己職位
and I'm not gonna Sully her good name
就毀了她的名聲
just to save my political hide.
毀了她  Janelle上了紐約市市長
Sully? Janelle bagged the mayor of New York City!
我說的對吧  Janelle 擊個掌
Am I right, janelle? Give me some!
我們還需努力
We'll work on it.
為什么來這 我以為我們是去吃午餐
Why are we stopping here? I thought we were going to lunch.
Bennet 我們得談談
Oh, Bennet. We need to talk.
Carter 我覺得我們一致同意我們不能
Yo, Carter, I thought we agreed we wasn't gonna...
沒事 這些是我的朋友
it's all right. These are my friends.
所以他們知道咱倆的事
Oh, so they know about us.
上帝啊 是一個基佬拳擊手
Oh, my God. It's a gay boxer.
Bennet 你是什么重量級的
Hey, Bennet. What weight class you fighting at?
輕量級
Uh, light-heavy.
我覺得你是巡洋艦級別的
I had you pegged for cruiser.
好主意 Stuart
That's a great idea, Stuart.
嘲笑職業的拳擊手
Taunt the professional ass-kicker.
我可不怕他
I'm not afraid of him.
我在大學也打過拳擊
You know, I used to box in college.
你可真高估了自己
You are way out of your league.
有人聞到了嗎
Does anybody else smell that?
沒有
No.
沒人聞到任何氣味
No one smells anything.
我可聞到了膽小鬼的氣味
No? I definitely smell a chicken.
先生們 這是一場公平公正的比賽
All right, men. I want a clean fight.
開始吧
Let's get it on.
等等 他要戴這對拳擊手套嗎
Wait a minute. Is he gonna use those gloves?
我的手套怎么了
What's wrong with my gloves?
它們不會影響
Well, won't they get in the way
那些抓撓拍打嗎
of all the scratching and slapping?
你會干倒他
You are gonna rock his world.
教訓他 你是真正的贏家
Punish him! You're the man!
祝你好運
Good luck.
來嘛 Stuey
Come on, stuey.
哇 你就像只狂野的小野獸
Ooh, you're like a wild animal, aren't ya?
如果你老是像個娘們一樣轉圈
Well, how am I supposed to fight you
我怎么和你打
if you keep running around like a sissy?
娘們
A sissy?
耶 他倒地了嗎
Yeah! Is he down?
他是你鐵哥們兒嗎
How good of a friend is he?
事實上 我們親如一家
Actually, we're very tight, but
但是你把他打得屁滾尿流我也不介意
I'm totally ok with you beating the crap out of him.
厄
Oomph!
厄 厄
Ooh! Ooh!
Oomph! Ooomph!
厄
Ooomph!
厄 加油啊 桃樂茜
Oooh. Come on, Dorothy.
<綠野仙蹤>女主人公的名字
你就這點能耐了嗎
Is that all you got?
好的 吃我一擊"還你漂漂拳"
Ok. Here comes one from Macy's basement.
唔吼
Woo-hoo!
1 2
1...2...
3 4
3...4...
別擔心 只有14個回合了 加油
Don't sweat this. Only 14 more rounds to go. Here we go!
你怎么樣 Stu 你還能行嗎
How ya doin', stu? You all right? Mmm.
這是幾根手指 說兩根
How many fingers am I holding up? Say 2.
- 兩根  - 他沒事
- 2.  - He's fine.
快點
Come on...
來啊
Bring it.
你不是基佬
You're not gay.
我是
Oh, yes I am.
我只是想先做一個拳擊手
I just want to be a boxer first.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
伙計們
Hey, fellas?
我想我能幫上忙 跟我來
I think I can help. Come with me.
你愿意去一場電影首映式嗎
How'd you like to go to a movie premiere?
我受傷了
I'm hurt.
你是Janelle Cooper 市長的女朋友
Hey, you're janelle Cooper, the mayor's girlfriend.
你剛說什么
Hey, what did you just say?!
淡定 市長和我
Calm down. Look, the mayor and I
就只有過一次非正式約會 沒其他了
had a casual date, but that's it.
這是我的新男朋友 Bennet Jones
This is my new boyfriend, Bennet Jones.
他是一個拳擊手
He's a boxer.
我不敢相信 Janelle愿意為了我這樣做
I can't believe that janelle agreed to do this for me.
她真的很在乎你 先生
She really cares about you, sir.
看 他們親的很帶勁哈
Boy, they're really hamming up that kiss, huh?
確實很帶勁
Yeah, yeah they are.
也許他們心里想的是我們
Probably thinking about us, huh?
看 先生
Yeah, look, sir.
她在抓你的屁股
She's grabbing your butt.
更多的地下情
Ahhh, more secret relationships.
- 你又贏了  - 我沒有贏
- You win again.  - I don't win.
Nikki 和你在一起我很驕傲
Look, Nikki, I'm proud of being with you.
我是這世界上最幸運的男人
I'm the luckiest guy in the world. I just...
我只是還需要一點時間
I just need a little more time.
但我想要別人知道我們的事
But I want everyone to know about us.
看到沒 這就是不同之處
Ok, see? There's the difference.
我需要 你想要
I need. You want.
需求永遠高于愿望
See, need always beats want.
胡扯
That's ridiculous.
不是 我需要肝臟移植
No, it's not. I need a liver transplant.
你想要一個肉桂卷
You want a sticky bun.
很明顯 我們意見不同
Clearly, we just disagree.
我們只能不停的爭論沒有結果
I think we're just gonna have to keep talking about this.
這算是吵架嗎
Does this count as an argument,
因為 你知道 我們從沒有過"和好嘿咻"
because, you know, we've never really had make-up sex.
噢
Ohhhh.
所以你想要做愛
So you want to have sex.
不過我需要你先說出來
But I need you to say it first.
當然可以 Nikki 我想
Well, sure, Nikki, I want...
不不不 不是現在 等等
no... no... no. Not yet. Not yet.
現在
Now.
噢
Ahhhh...
我 我想做愛
I... I want to have sex.
心里有人選了嗎 Mike
With anyone in particular, Mike?
沒有 我只是想表達一下自己的觀點
No, I'm just making a general statement.
我想做愛
I wanna have sex.
我想要一個肉丸三明治
I wanna have a meatball sandwich.
你來求我啦
You come for a fix?
不是 我已經擺脫那些醬汁了
Nope. I'm off the sauce.
真的 你怎么做到的
Really? And how'd you do it?
我運用了在心理課上學到的一個原理
I applied a principle that I learned in psych class
叫做暴露療法
called exposure therapy.
什么意思
And what does that mean?
就是說我吃了四百個肉丸
It means I ate 400 meatballs.
為了致歉 我的祖母
To apologize, my grandmother...
她給你做了些巧克力曲奇
She made you some chocolate chip cookies.
謝謝
Thank you.
太好吃了
Oh, that's good.
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組